http://www.henrywilliamson.co.uk/57-uncategorised/86-privacy-notice

The Henry Williamson Society
ContactsHomeAbout UsLinks
Privacy Notice
PRIVACY NOTICE
1.  In accordance with the requirements of the General Data Protection Regulation 2018 (GDPR) the Henry Williamson Society (hereinafter ‘The Society’) collects data from its members for the purpose of giving notice of Society events and issue of the annual Journal, Newsletter and ad hoc publications. This data comprises name, address, landline/mobile telephone numbers, and also email address and Gift Aid declaration (if applicable) which are held both on an electronic database and as a paper record.
2.  The Society recognises the importance of protecting members’ privacy with the database and paper record being held and managed by the membership secretary only. The Society has a strict policy of not selling or trading any information about its members, customers or prospective customers to any company, organisation or person outside the Society.
3.  Members’ personal data will only be used for the duration of the individual’s or family’s membership. Following notification of cessation of membership all personal information will be deleted within one month of the date of notification. If membership is not renewed and there is no response to two written reminders sent within three months of the renewal date that membership will be deleted one month after the second reminder.
4.  Under the terms of the GDPR Society members have the right to request sight of the information held on them by the Society, and can do so by contacting the membership secretary. As the basis on which this information is held is consent (current members are all considered to have consented to their data being held and therefore to have ‘opted in’ under the terms of the GDPR) members can request that any part of the data held on them is rectified or deleted at any time, by means of application to the membership secretary. After 25 May 2018 membership applications from children under 16 will require, in addition to their own consent, consent from a person holding parental responsibility.
5 (i)  The Society’s website collates hit data, but this information is not forwarded to or shared with any third party, only technical data such as domain name, country, browser, computer operating system and internet browser being recorded. Cookies are issued from our website so that members will not have to repeatedly enter user names and passwords when visiting different parts of the website, and also to retain user preference information. If you do not know what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit http://www.aboutcookies.org for detailed guidance.
5 (ii)  The Society’s website enables members to pay for products or services online with a credit card, via a link to PayPal. Unless otherwise noted, these transactions are encrypted and any personal and other confidential information you enter in the transaction is used only for the purposes described in that transaction. The Society does not keep your credit card information. All PayPal transactions are subject to the PayPal Privacy Policy.
5 (iii)  This privacy notice applies only to the Society’s website and members should read the privacy statements on any other websites they may visit, including those accessed via links from the Society’s website, the privacy notices of which the Society is not responsible for.
(Updated 24/5/2018)
HomeHenry WilliamsonA Writer's LifeKey DatesExtracts from his worksA Life's WorkHW and the First World WarBiographyEarly DaysFirst World WarMove to GeorgehamThe Early TwentiesThe Hawthornden PrizeShallowford DaysThe Norfolk FarmReturn to DevonAncient SunlightLast DaysBibliographyIntroductionA Life's WorkBooks by HWBooks about HWSociety PublicationsCopyrightResearch CentreIntroductionAuthor IndexTitle IndexSocietyAbout the SocietyConstitutionSociety AimsJournal and NewsletterSociety PublicationsSociety ArchiveLocal BranchesJoin the SocietySociety EventsIntroductionAutumn Meeting, October 2020Schools' Writing CompetitionSchools' Writing Competition 20202018 Results2016 Results2014 Results2012 Results2010 Results2008 Results2006 ResultsContactsExternal Links
Online Bookshop
Books
E-books
Second-hand books
Journals
Other merchandise
Shopping Cart
x
Henry Williamson Society © 2001-2020, Registered Charity No. 288168.
Photographs © The Henry Williamson Literary Estate unless
otherwise stated.
